Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas)
1952-2001
1981-1991
New York University Archives
Brademas, John, 1927-2016
New York University. Office of the President
RG.3.0.10
134.50 Linear Feet in 307 manuscript boxes, 4 flat boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 1 flat-file folder.
36 VHS
1 audiocassette
John Brademas (1927-2016) was born and raised in Indiana, and later represented the Third District of Indiana in the United States House of Representatives from 1959 to 1980. After leaving public office, Brademas accepted the position of President of New York University (NYU), serving from 1981 to 1992. The Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) contain files related to the daily administration of the office of the President. Records in this collection include Brademas' daily schedule; event material; speeches; correspondence; funder and institution subject files; Board of Trustees material; reports and communications on NYU Schools and Divisions; files on student groups; audiovisual recordings of speeches and events; and publicity material. The collection also contains publicity photographs of professors, students, and NYU locations in other countries.
Conditions Governing Access
University Archives staff will review all requested material before providing access.
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Individual restricted files in open series are notated in the file title (e.g., "Correspondence RESTRICTED"), physically separated, and stored in shared restricted boxes.
Series VII. Governance files are closed until December 31, 2027.
The following series are closed and access is restricted:
Series IV. Development
Series VI. Finance
Series XIV. Correspondence
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials were transferred in multiple accessions. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 12.009, 12.017, 13.002, 13.029, 13.040, 13.041, 14.002, 14.006, 2016.003, 2016.040, 2017.004, 2017.005, 2017.045, 2017.048, 2019.041, and 2022.043, and 2024.028.
Appraisal
On 1/21/2020, three cartons of duplicate material were removed and shredded as previously agreed upon by the University Archivist.
On 2/2020, one carton of audiovisual material and one carton of NYU publications were removed from the collection, deaccessioned, and sent back to the University Archivist.
On 2/27/2020, 21 boxes of personnel files were removed from the collection, deaccessioned, and shredded.
Arrangement
Material was not arranged by the processing archivist, but remains in the order in which it was received.
The records are arranged into 14 series. The series arrangement of the records is as follows:
Series I. Administration
Series II. Alumni Affairs
Series III. Associations
Series IV. Development
Series V. Facilities and Services
Series VI. Finance
Series VII. Governance
Series VIII. Governmental Relations
Series IX. Art and Memorabilia
Series X. Public Relations
Series XI. Schools and Divisions
Series XII. Student Affairs
Series XIII. Speeches and Writings
Series XIV. Correspondence
Series XV. Publicity Photographs
Biographical Note
Stephen John Brademas, Jr. (1927-2016) was born in Mishawaka, Indiana to Beatrice Goble Brademas, a schoolteacher, and Stephen John Brademas, Sr., a Greek-immigrant restaurateur. Brademas graduated from South Bend Central High School and entered the University of Notre Dame in 1945, but soon left to join the Navy where he was appointed to the Naval Reserve Officers Training Corps until May 1946. In September of that year, he entered Harvard College and in 1949 graduated with a B.A. in Government. From 1950 to 1953, he studied as a Rhodes Scholar at Oxford University, England, where he received a Doctor of Philosophy in Social Studies.
From 1959 to 1980, Brademas represented the Third District of Indiana in the United States House of Representatives. He served on the Education and Labor Committee, the House Administration Committee, and the Joint Committee on the Library of Congress. Brademas played a principal role in writing major legislation concerning all forms of education, including elementary, collegiate, and vocational training. He was also a major proponent of legislation for services for the elderly and handicapped, as well as Federal support for cultural institutions and the arts. In January 1973, Brademas was appointed Chief Deputy Majority Whip and in 1977 was appointed Majority Whip, a position he held for the next four years.
After leaving public office, Brademas accepted the position of President of New York University (NYU), serving from 1981 to 1992. During his tenure, he worked to change NYU from a primarily commuter school by facilitating the construction or purchase of 11 residence halls, which by the time he left, housed 44 percent of the NYU student population. Under his guidance, NYU also added new academic programs including the Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies and the Skirball Department of Hebrew and Judaic Studies. During his tenure, Brademas established NYU programs in Cyprus, Egypt, France, Israel and Japan. In July of 1990, he announced his resignation and officially stepped down from his position, becoming president emeritus in 1992 after a sabbatical.
After leaving NYU, Brademas served as chairman of the President's Committee on the Arts and the Humanities from 1994 to 2001. From 2004 to 2007, he was a member of the New York State Board of Regents. In 2005, NYU established the John Brademas Center of New York University, a research and teaching facility. He was the recipient of more than 50 honorary degrees and awards, many conferred by European governments or cultural organizations. Brademas passed away in 2016.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact the University Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Related Materials
For additional material on John Brademas, see also: the John Brademas Personal Papers (MC 241) and the John Brademas Congressional Papers (MC 168).
Scope and Contents
The collection contains records of New York University's 13th President John Brademas who served from 1981 to 1991. Files created by Brademas' office contain material related to the responsibilities of this position, including public appearances and events; contact with various NYU Schools and Divisions staff; interaction with student groups and representatives; and fostering NYU's relationships with various governmental departments and other organizations as they relate to funding and/or educational policy for universities.
Files in this collection include Brademas' speeches and remarks; NYU Board meeting material; and public relations event planning files which include video recordings related to NYU's acquisition of the La Pietra villa. Additionally, this collection contains internal and external communications, reports, and meeting notes related to NYU facilities, NYU Schools and Divisions, and student groups. Files accumulated by Brademas on individuals, organizations, and companies document his relationships cultivated for the purpose of fundraising, educational policy support, and NYU program development. Although a selection of Brademas' chronological correspondence has its own series, a significant amount of topical correspondence can be found throughout the entire collection.
Pre-1981 office files in this collection were likely a carry-over from the previous President's office and used for reference by Brademas and his staff. Material dated beyond Brademas' term found in this collection covers projects he continued for NYU working as president emeritus, after officially leaving office in 1991.
This collection also includes photographs and negatives of professors, students, and NYU locations in other countries. These photographs may have been used in NYU publications. Countries highlighted in the photographs and negatives include the United Kingdom, Italy, France, and Afghanistan. The photographs of professors consist of portraits and candid shots. There are also several oversized photographs of President Jay Oliva.
Separated Materials
21 boxes of files were transferred to the John Brademas Personal Papers (MC 241); one record carton of files was transferred to the John Brademas Congressional Papers (MC 168); and one record carton of files was transferred to the Records of the Office of the President (Dr. James McNaughton Hester) (RG 3.0.7).
Education, Higher.; Education -- New York (State) -- New York.; College Presidents -- New York (State); Private universities and colleges -- Administration -- United States.; Speeches (documents); Correspondence.; Photographs.; Negatives.; Foreign study; Promotional materials; Alexander S. Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies; New York University. Skirball Department of Hebrew and Judaic Studies; New York University -- Speeches; New York University -- Students
- Series I. Administration, 1973-2001; 9.60 Linear Feet in 23 manuscript boxes.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Brademas' appointment books from 1981 to 1991, documenting his daily events and meetings. Other files include material related to the Bobst Award; honorary degrees; selection process for departmental chairs and visiting professors; fundraising; and university program development. Information on NYU's overseas programs; the Urban Studies and Research Center; the Grey Art Gallery; and the Japanese Business Center are in this series. The "JB Project" files appear to be ideas fostered by Brademas, including a Chinese University Presidents' group visit to NYU and a potential Latin American Foreign Ministers Conference. Brademas' travel briefing books in this series were created for his trips taken between 1989 to 1990 to Greece, Cyprus, and France. These briefing books typically contain schedules, support material for meetings, and profiles on people he would meet during the trip. Similar travel briefing material can also be found in Series VII.
  - Academic Matters, 1981, 2001, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Matters RESTRICTED, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Statistical Reports, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Juan Carlos Professor and Possibility of Degree to Charles, Prince of Wales, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Civil Rights Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Book #1 -- Briefing, Japan Itinerary, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Book #1 -- Briefing, Japan Itinerary RESTRICTED, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - John Merck Scholars Program, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic Freedom, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic Freedom and Federal Censorship of Research, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University of the Witwatersrand, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University of the Witwatersrand -- Complaint Against Faculty RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Awards and Prizes, A - M, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Awards and Prizes, N - Z, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Awards, Fellowships, Citations, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Awards, Fellowships, Citations, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Awards, Fellowships, Citations RESTRICTED, 1980-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Andres Segovia, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Fellowships, Awards, Citations, 1984-1986, undated (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Outside Awards Given to NYU Students and Faculty, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
  - Outside Awards Given to NYU Students, Faculty RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - University Agendas, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Awards and Prizes: Elmer Holmes Bobst Literary Prize, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Prizes: University Medal, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bobst Awards, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 3-6)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7-10)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Honorary Degrees -- Received, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Honorary Degrees RESTRICTED, 1980-1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Honorary Degree Candidates, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Father Tim Healy, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Communication on Coordinated Studies, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chairs (A - Z), 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Raul Alfonsin -- Convocation Arrangements, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence -- Raymond Carr RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Naming Opportunities, Other Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Naming Opportunities and Other Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Re: Department Chairs RESTRICTED, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Re: Department Chairs, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Re: Department Chairs, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Juan Carlos Chair, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Visiting Professors, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Berlowitz Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Michael Eisenstadt -- Diplomat in Residence, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Program Development, 1981-08-01-1982-09-30 (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
  - Program Development, 1981-07-01-1982-03-31 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Program Development, 1982-04-01-1982-12-31 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Program Development, 1982-10-01-1982-10-31 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Program Development (NYU and Oxford Exchange Program), 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Program Development, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Program Development RESTRICTED, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
  - Program Development RESTRICTED, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising Correspondence, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Various Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Preliminary Report of African-American Activities, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Committee on Urban Studies RESTRICTED, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Greek Cultural Center RESTRICTED, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Japanese Business Center (and Related Trips to Japan), 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 8-9, Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Japanese Business Center (and Related Trips to Japan) RESTRICTED, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Japanese-American Relations, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Japanese Business Center (and Related Trips to Japan), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
  - Japanese Business Center (and Related Trips to Japan) RESTRICTED, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Japan RESTRICTED, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Jewish Resource Center, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence -- Jewish Resource Center RESTRICTED, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Hebrew Union College and NYU, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Hebrew and Judaic Studies -- National Jewish Resource Center, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hebrew and Judaic Studies, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Hebrew and Judaic Studies RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Catalan Program, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Journalism Center, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Catalan Studies, 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
  - Academic Matters and China Exchange, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - China Exchange, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - China Exchange RESTRICTED, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - International Collaborations, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Urban Studies Center, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 4-6)
  - Urban Studies Center RESTRICTED, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Fordham, City, Columbia, New School Consortia Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - City University, Columbia University (Teachers College), Fordham, St. Johns, NYU Consortial Program, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Research University Caucus, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Model Faculty Resource Network, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Town Hall, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Exchange (NYU-Oxford), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller U. and NYU Humanities Program, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller U. and NYU Joint Program in the Humanities, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Yugoslavia and Juan Carlos Center, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Yugoslavia, Juan Carlos Chair RESTRICTED, 1982-1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Yugoslavia Program RESTRICTED, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Free University, Berlin, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Berlin and NY Project, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Oxford Exchange Program, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Joaquin Romero -- Maura and Spanish House Discussion, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - American Institutions Program, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - European Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Interest and Expertise on Africa, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Chair in Canadian Studies Proposal, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - United Nations Proposals, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Eastern European Training Institute Project, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Grey Art Collection, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Art Collection, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Altshuler Collection, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Grey Art Collection in Athens, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Art Collections: Loans, 1973-1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Art Collection -- Borrowed by President's Office, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Art Work Donation by French President, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Grey Gallery Affairs, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Grey Art Gallery, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Exhibitions, 1987-1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Exhibitions RESTRICTED, 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Model Faculty Resource Network and Hellenic Cultural Center, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hellenic Cultural Center RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Announcements and Memos, 1977-1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Announcements and Circular Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Task Force and Drug Problems, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action Recruitment, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence -- Marketing, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Consultants, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - NYU Opposition to Tax Proposals, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Endowment Statistics, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (Some with Spelman College), 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence -- Problems with Foreign Governments, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Scholars Visiting From Abroad Study, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Re: University Archives, Archivist, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Legal Matters RESTRICTED, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Legal RESTRICTED, 1981-1990 (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
  - Legal Opinions RESTRICTED, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Buetner-Janusch RESTRICTED, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Cantor Lawsuit RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence -- Real Estate RESTRICTED, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Libraries RESTRICTED, 1979-1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Libraries, 1979-1986 (Box 10, Folder 19-22)
  - Libraries, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Libraries, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Libraries -- Procedures, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cooperation and Libraries, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Cooperation and Libraries RESTRICTED, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Libraries, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Office Services, 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Office Services Equipment and Supplies, 1975-1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Office Services Equipment and Supplies RESTRICTED, 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Office Services Equipment and Supplies, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Office Services and Mail, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Mail Problems, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Office of Sponsored Programs, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - University Planning Commission, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Research and Planning, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Various Studies, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Various Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Greek -- US Cultural Exchange -- Larry Tisch, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Research and Planning Reports, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Administration Issues, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Registrar's Annual Report and Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Donor RESTRICTED, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Actual Cost Allocation Report, Sections A - E, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Academic Matters and Computers, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Telephone Study, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - NYU Laboratory for Experimental Medicine and Surgery in Primates, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Medical Center, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Appointment Books, 1981-1982 (Box 124)
  - Appointment Books, 1983-1985 (Box 125)
  - Appointment Schedule -- Supporting Material, July 1985 (Box 225, Folder 3-4)
  - Appointment Books, 1986-1987 (Box 126)
  - Calendar, October - December, 1987 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1988 (Box 224, Folder 2-3)
  - Appointment Book, September -- December, 1988 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 224, Folder 5-6)
  - Appointment Book, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 1-2)
  - Daily Schedule and Notes, 1990-07-17-1990-07-25 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - NYU Varsity Club Hall of Fame, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Political Issues Committee, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - War Powers Briefing Book, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 3-4)
  - Brademas Congressional Papers Discussion, 1986-1987 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - JB Project -- Prince of Wales and Harvard's 350th Anniversary, 1986 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - JB Project -- Yugoslavia Link via US Embassy and Graduate School of Business Administration, 1986 (Box 127, Folder 7-8)
  - JB Project -- Visit of Chinese University Presidents, 1986 (Box 127, Folder 9-10, Box 128, Folder 1-3)
  - JB Project -- Latin American Foreign Ministers Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 128, Folder 4-5)
  - JB Project -- Paul Hirsch -- Argentina Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - JB Project -- (Antonis) Tritsis Visit, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Press Clippings on Various Topics, with Notes, 1985-1990 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Press Clippings on Brademas, 1985-1990 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Biographical Sketch, November 1989 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - NYU and Spain, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 6-7)
  - Press Clippings Re: End of Cold War, German Reunification, 1989-1990 (Box 130, Folder 1)